[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie", "Mark Halperin", "John Heilemann"], "LOCATION": ["Romney Campaign"]}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "JJR", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "What are the juiciest tidbits you have in from the last few hours?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "juiciest", "tidbits", "you", "have", "in", "from", "the", "last", "few", "hours", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "Well, one of the big things has come out, you mentioned Chris Christie earlier is that someone in the Romney Campaign apparently turned over their vice- presidential vetting file to the authors Mark Halperin and John Heilemann.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "one", "of", "the", "big", "things", "has", "come", "out", ",", "you", "mentioned", "Chris", "Christie", "earlier", "is", "that", "someone", "in", "the", "Romney", "Campaign", "apparently", "turned", "over", "their", "vice-", "presidential", "vetting", "file", "to", "the", "authors", "Mark", "Halperin", "and", "John", "Heilemann", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last few hours?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "I mean I presume Newt will now try and say the nice things to Governor Christie quite hard when you read that about yourself, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "I", "presume", "Newt", "will", "now", "try", "and", "say", "the", "nice", "things", "to", "Governor", "Christie", "quite", "hard", "when", "you", "read", "that", "about", "yourself", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Newt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["New Jersey Governor"], "LOCATION": ["Virginia"]}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Any surprises in store or is it pretty much in the bag you think?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "surprises", "in", "store", "or", "is", "it", "pretty", "much", "in", "the", "bag", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "It's pretty much in the bag with the two big races as they are every off of year or the New Jersey Governor's race and the Virginia race.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "pretty", "much", "in", "the", "bag", "with", "the", "two", "big", "races", "as", "they", "are", "every", "off", "of", "year", "or", "the", "New", "Jersey", "Governor", "'s", "race", "and", "the", "Virginia", "race", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "What is your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "It was a tough campaign.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "tough", "campaign", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "ORGAN: Has he gone fat to Chris Christie to say sorry or explain himself?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Has", "he", "gone", "fat", "to", "Chris", "Christie", "to", "say", "sorry", "or", "explain", "himself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2016"]}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "Do you need somebody that can raise for the White House who has that ability?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "need", "somebody", "that", "can", "raise", "for", "the", "White", "House", "who", "has", "that", "ability", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Well, as you know, because we've talked about it before, I think governors have an advantage in running for the nomination in 2016.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "as", "you", "know", ",", "because", "we", "'ve", "talked", "about", "it", "before", ",", "I", "think", "governors", "have", "an", "advantage", "in", "running", "for", "the", "nomination", "in", "2016", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "Is there any doubt, Newt, to think that she's going to run -- Hillary Clinton?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "doubt", ",", "Newt", ",", "to", "think", "that", "she", "'s", "going", "to", "run", "--", "Hillary", "Clinton", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Look.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Newt"], "PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "And how do you fix it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "do", "you", "fix", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Is he deeply unpleasant as everyone tries to say he is?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "deeply", "unpleasant", "as", "everyone", "tries", "to", "say", "he", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "He is a guy that needs to know his place with you.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "is", "a", "guy", "that", "needs", "to", "know", "his", "place", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Martin"]}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "If you were going into battle tomorrow again say the New York Giants and you could choose either Richie Incognito or Jonathan Martin to be alongside you, who would you go for?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "going", "into", "battle", "tomorrow", "again", "say", "the", "New", "York", "Giants", "and", "you", "could", "choose", "either", "Richie", "Incognito", "or", "Jonathan", "Martin", "to", "be", "alongside", "you", ",", "who", "would", "you", "go", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNPS", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "I would go with Martin.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "go", "with", "Martin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["New York Giants"], "PERSON": ["Richie Incognito", "Jonathan Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Glenn Greenwald"]}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "RBR", ":", "RB", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Were would you draw the line?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "would", "you", "draw", "the", "line", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "Well, I think Glenn Greenwald has been very much more -- far more eloquent than I could be about the issue.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "Glenn", "Greenwald", "has", "been", "very", "much", "more", "--", "far", "more", "eloquent", "than", "I", "could", "be", "about", "the", "issue", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RBR", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "What do you think of that, is that another example is letting you down on transparency?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", ",", "is", "that", "another", "example", "is", "letting", "you", "down", "on", "transparency", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "I don't know enough about that, I didn't know that, but I was very disappoint when he said, you know, you could trust us and he implied that we will fix this thing and it's like, you know, that he is lying and on top of that, you asked earlier is he in control of it, I don't think that he is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "enough", "about", "that", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "know", "that", ",", "but", "I", "was", "very", "disappoint", "when", "he", "said", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "could", "trust", "us", "and", "he", "implied", "that", "we", "will", "fix", "this", "thing", "and", "it", "'s", "like", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "he", "is", "lying", "and", "on", "top", "of", "that", ",", "you", "asked", "earlier", "is", "he", "in", "control", "of", "it", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "he", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "Do you remember it vividly, where were you when it happened?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "it", "vividly", ",", "where", "were", "you", "when", "it", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "I was in boarding school.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "in", "boarding", "school", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Is America a better or worst country now than it was in the '60s?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "America", "a", "better", "or", "worst", "country", "now", "than", "it", "was", "in", "the", "'60s", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "DT", "JJR", "CC", "JJS", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Well, I -- from my point of view, when I was -- I didn't know what I knew then.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "--", "from", "my", "point", "of", "view", ",", "when", "I", "was", "--", "I", "did", "n't", "know", "what", "I", "knew", "then", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "What makes you so convinced that Lee Harvey Oswald did not attack alone?", "question_tokens": ["What", "makes", "you", "so", "convinced", "that", "Lee", "Harvey", "Oswald", "did", "not", "attack", "alone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "When I was in the infantry, I saw men blown away.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "was", "in", "the", "infantry", ",", "I", "saw", "men", "blown", "away", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lee Harvey Oswald"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Do we ever know which one (ph)?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "we", "ever", "know", "which", "one", "(", "ph", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WDT", "CD", "CD", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Well, you can keep saying that but, you know, people have dig in all the time, and there aren't always records.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "can", "keep", "saying", "that", "but", ",", "you", "know", ",", "people", "have", "dig", "in", "all", "the", "time", ",", "and", "there", "are", "n't", "always", "records", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Roosevelt", "Roosevelt"], "LOCATION": ["Kennedy"]}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "... more than once in your lifetime, who would you have?", "question_tokens": ["...", "more", "than", "once", "in", "your", "lifetime", ",", "who", "would", "you", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "JJR", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Well, I like Roosevelt and Kennedy I would -- I did not experience Roosevelt.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "like", "Roosevelt", "and", "Kennedy", "I", "would", "--", "I", "did", "not", "experience", "Roosevelt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "JJR", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "EX", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP$", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", ":", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "To be a great rock legend, do you have to have a dash of fashion (inaudible) about you?", "question_tokens": ["To", "be", "a", "great", "rock", "legend", ",", "do", "you", "have", "to", "have", "a", "dash", "of", "fashion", "(", "inaudible", ")", "about", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Not that you have to you can be a great song writer and great singer but that's swagger, that extra swagger something that becomes more memorable and it adds to the stage performance, and as of that your presence is there and it adds to your, you know, your -- how people view you I think in the public side.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "that", "you", "have", "to", "you", "can", "be", "a", "great", "song", "writer", "and", "great", "singer", "but", "that", "'s", "swagger", ",", "that", "extra", "swagger", "something", "that", "becomes", "more", "memorable", "and", "it", "adds", "to", "the", "stage", "performance", ",", "and", "as", "of", "that", "your", "presence", "is", "there", "and", "it", "adds", "to", "your", ",", "you", "know", ",", "your", "--", "how", "people", "view", "you", "I", "think", "in", "the", "public", "side", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "What is the solution to Detroit's problems you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "solution", "to", "Detroit", "'s", "problems", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "Well if I knew that, you know I think it's tough.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "if", "I", "knew", "that", ",", "you", "know", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "tough", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Detroit"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "It's establish -- should more great Americans success stories be thinking more into stop out sourcing so much?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "establish", "--", "should", "more", "great", "Americans", "success", "stories", "be", "thinking", "more", "into", "stop", "out", "sourcing", "so", "much", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ":", "MD", "JJR", "JJ", "NNPS", "NN", "NNS", "VB", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "I think we are.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "we", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Eric Clapton"], "LOCATION": ["Jimmy Hendrix"]}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "ORGAN: Really, why him?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Really", ",", "why", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "You know first of all musically he shattered everything that was out there at the time when he came on all of the great artist whether it was the Beatles or Eric Clapton at the time of the who they were all afraid of Jimmy Hendrix because he was so powerful musically.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "first", "of", "all", "musically", "he", "shattered", "everything", "that", "was", "out", "there", "at", "the", "time", "when", "he", "came", "on", "all", "of", "the", "great", "artist", "whether", "it", "was", "the", "Beatles", "or", "Eric", "Clapton", "at", "the", "time", "of", "the", "who", "they", "were", "all", "afraid", "of", "Jimmy", "Hendrix", "because", "he", "was", "so", "powerful", "musically", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Is there any chance?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "chance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]